{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "A: Where's John?\nB: I'm not sure. He _________ in the kitchen.",
            "a": "might be",
            "b": "can be",
            "c": "would be",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "21",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kate wanted to have a dog, but her landlord _________ let her keep one in the flat.",
            "a": "shouldn't",
            "b": "wouldn't",
            "c": "needn't",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "21",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I spoke to Anna yesterday, I promised that I ___ send her the information she wanted.",
            "a": "would",
            "b": "must",
            "c": "will",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "21",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Haven't you finished writing your letter yet? You _________ it for two hours!",
            "a": "must be writing",
            "b": "could have been writing",
            "c": "must have been writing",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "21",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The library ___ closed. Nobody's answering the phone.",
            "a": "can't be",
            "b": "must be",
            "c": "needn't be",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "21",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ___ pay any attention to what John has told you about Katie. He doesn't know her very well.",
            "a": "mustn't",
            "b": "shouldn't",
            "c": "couldn't",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "21",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I demanded that Paul ___ tell me the truth.",
            "a": "must",
            "b": "has to",
            "c": "should",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "21",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ___ spill water on anything electrical, like televisions or CD players.",
            "a": "needn't",
            "b": "couldn't",
            "c": "mustn't",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "21",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sarah made a lot of food for her party, but her guests ate only about half of it. She ___ so much.",
            "a": "couldn't have made",
            "b": "needn't have made",
            "c": "mustn't have made",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "21",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "A friend tells you the name of a new restaurant, and she spells it for you. You don't write it all down, so you ask her: '___ you spell it again, please?'",
            "a": "Would",
            "b": "Should",
            "c": "Might",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "21",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}